# RANDY HEMBRADOR

San Francisco, CA, 94105 | Phone: 928-787-7395 | Email: <a href="mailto:randy.hembrador@gmail.com">randy.hembrador@gmail.com</a> LinkedIn: <a href="mailto://in/randy-hembrador-39a3145/">/in/randy-hembrador-39a3145/</a> | Portfolio: <a href="mailto:www.randyhembrador.com">www.randyhembrador.com</a>

#### **SUMMARY**

UX/UI Designer with a certificate in UX/UI from UC Berkeley and strong language & analysis skills from a career in legal support. Has extensive experience working with global software development teams, fluency in multimedia applications and front-end development technologies, a systems-oriented mindset, and a love for storytelling & collaboration. Searching for roles that continue to develop strengths in information architecture, writing, and/or developing interactive prototypes.

#### **SKILLS**

**Technical:** Figma (including components, libraries, and variants), HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, SCSS, JQuery, GitHub, Unreal Engine, Google Apps Script, Adobe Creative Suite, Slack, Confluence, Trello, JIRA, Google Drive, Google Workspace, Microsoft Office, Asana, Airtable, Miro, Whimsical

**UX/UI:** UX Research, Heuristic Evaluation, Information Architecture, User Interface Design, Research Interviews and Analysis, User Personas, Storyboarding, Flow Diagrams, Prototyping and Wireframing, Interaction Design, Usability Testing, Remote User Testing

**Theoretical:** Atomic Design, Typography, Color Theory, Responsive Design, MVC Design, Web Development, Marketing Concepts, Agile Processes, Project Management

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **ELECTRONIC ARTS INC. (Redwood City, CA)**

Senior Legal Approval Associate (Non-Attorney)

Analyzed upcoming product and marketing designs for compliance concerns;

collaborated with global cross-functional stakeholders to resolve them.

- Researched compliance workflows for internal business clients and identified actionable causes for multiple pain-points
- Designed and developed ticketing systems for personally supported products that increased support lead times by 1-6 months and streamlined conversations by 20-80%
- Received award grants from leadership for devising information architecture that unblocked progress on 2 large internal projects



 Received an award grant from leadership for devising and leading whiteboard exercises that enabled better understanding and support for an emergent business unit's product

## Senior IP Associate (Non-Attorney)

January 2007 - June 2015

Conducted research on content-use by competitors and other entities; provided analyses and summaries of findings.

Represent Legal in biweekly cross-functional sprint planning sessions.

• Overhauled a Legal organization SharePoint site by designing new information architecture and developing custom HTML & CSS page templates

## WILSON, SONSINI, GOODRICH & ROSATI, PC (Palo Alto, CA)

Patent File Clerk

April 2004 - June 2006

Provide records retrieval support; render illustrations and schematics for patent applications

• Helped set up the filing system and trained personnel at a satellite office

## SEREFINA, LLC (San Mateo, CA)

Freelance Web Designer and Developer (Contract Project) April 2014 - October 2014

Designed, developed, and launched the direct-to-consumer site for a fashion accessory company now sold at major retailers including Anthropologie and Club Monaco.

- Site has generated up to \$48,000 in daily sales with only a minimal initial need for post-launch support.
- Conducted stakeholder interviews with company leadership to identify business needs and determine potential solutions
- Developed information architecture deliverables including a site map and a content audit; results of the audit were adopted afterward as the foundation for general inventory management
- Developed custom responsive Bootstrap-based page templates

### **EDUCATION**

University of California, Berkeley (August 2021) Certificate, UX/UI

University of California, Davis (June 2001) Bachelor of Arts, Fine Arts; Bachelor of Arts, Psychology

